<copyright>
    <files license="MIT">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2005-2019 Rich Felker <dalias@aerifal.cx>
2005-2019 Many other contributors
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="public-domain">
        <file src="include/*"/>
        <file src="arch/*/bits/*"/>
        <file src="crt/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2005-2014 Rich Felker <dalias@aerifal.cx>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
The following files are trivial, in my opinion not copyrightable in
the first place, and hereby explicitly released to the Public Domain:

All public headers: include/*, arch/*/bits/*
Startup files: crt/*
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-clause">
        <file src="src/regex/reg*"/>
        <file src="src/regex/tre*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2001-2008 Ville Laurikari <vl@iki.fi>
2012 Rich Felker <dalias@aerifal.cx>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="ISC">
        <file src="src/math/tgammal.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/lgammal.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/powl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/logl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log2l.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log1pl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log10l.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/erfl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/expm1l.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/expl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/__polevll.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008 Stephen L. Moshier <steve@moshier.net>
1993 Sun Microsystems, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-clause">
        <file src="src/math/fmal.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/fmaf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/fma.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/exp2l.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/exp2f.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/exp2.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2005-2011 David Schultz <das@freebsd.org>
1993 Sun Microsystems, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="permissive">
        <file src="src/math/tanf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/tan.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sqrtf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sqrt.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sinf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sincosf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sincos.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/sin.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/scalbf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/scalb.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/powf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/pow.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/logf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log2f.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log2.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log1pf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log1p.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log10f.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log10.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/log.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/lgammaf_r.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/lgamma_r.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/j*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/expm1f.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/expm1.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/expf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/exp.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/erf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/erff.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/cosf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/cos.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/cbrt*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/atanl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/atanf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/atan2*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/atan.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/asinl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/asinf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/asin.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/acosl.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/acosf.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/acos.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/__tan*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/__sin*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/__rem*.c"/>
        <file src="src/math/__cos*.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1993, 2004 Sun Microsystems, Inc.
2008, 2009-2011 Bruce D. Evans
2008, 2009-2011 Steven G. Kargl
2008, 2009-2011 David Schultz
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Developed at SunPro, a Sun Microsystems, Inc. business.
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this
software is freely granted, provided that this notice
is preserved.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="public-domain">
        <file src="src/crypt/crypt_blowfish.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1998-2012 Solar Designer <solar@openwall.com>
2012 Rich Felker <dalias@aerifal.cx>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Written by Solar Designer <solar at openwall.com> in 1998-2012.
No copyright is claimed, and the software is hereby placed in the public
domain.  In case this attempt to disclaim copyright and place the software
in the public domain is deemed null and void, then the software is
Copyright (c) 1998-2012 Solar Designer and it is hereby released to the
general public under the following terms:

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted.

There's ABSOLUTELY NO WARRANTY, express or implied.

It is my intent that you should be able to use this on your system,
as part of a software package, or anywhere else to improve security,
ensure compatibility, or for any other purpose.  I would appreciate
it if you give credit where it is due and keep your modifications in
the public domain as well, but I don't require that in order to let
you place this code and any modifications you make under a license
of your choice.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="src/crypt/crypt_des.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1994 David Burren
2000,2002,2010,2012 Solar Designer <solar@openwall.com>
2012 Rich Felker <dalias@aerifal.cx>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="MIT">
        <file src="src/stdlib/qsort.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2011 Valentin Ochs
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="MIT">
        <file src="src/setjmp/x32/longjmp.s"/>
        <file src="src/setjmp/x32/setjmp.s"/>
        <file src="src/setjmp/x86_64/longjmp.s"/>
        <file src="src/setjmp/x86_64/setjmp.s"/>
        <file src="src/thread/x32/__set_thread_area.s"/>
        <file src="src/thread/x32/__unmapself.s"/>
        <file src="src/thread/x86_64/__set_thread_area.s"/>
        <file src="src/thread/x86_64/__unmapself.s"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2011-2012 Nicholas J. Kain
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="MIT">
        <file src="arch/mips64/*"/>
        <file src="src/*/mips64/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2016 Mahesh Bodapati
2016 Jaydeep Patil
2016 Imagination Technologies
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-clause">
        <file src="src/string/arm/memcpy_le.S"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008 The Android Open Source Project
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="MIT"><![CDATA[
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a
copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"),
to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation
the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included
in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, 
TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE 
SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="ISC"><![CDATA[
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES
WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR
ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-2-clause"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER AND CONTRIBUTORS
``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-clause"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
3. Neither the name of the author nor the names of other contributors
   may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
   without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS'' AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
