<copyright>
    <files license="Fietkau">
        <file src="main.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2015 Felix Fietkau <nbd@openwrt.org>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Permission to use, copy, modify, and/or distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES
WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR
ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="PD-Fietkau">
        <file src="sha512.c"/>
        <file src="sha512.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2015 Felix Fietkau <nbd@openwrt.org>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
These files had been previously placed into the Public Domain and were then
relicensed (presumably after receiving some modifications and/or enhancements)
under the following license:

Permission to use, copy, modify, and/or distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES
WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR
ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="PD">
        <file src="ed25519.c"/>
        <file src="ed25519.h"/>
        <file src="edsign.c"/>
        <file src="edsign.h"/>
        <file src="f25519.c"/>
        <file src="f25519.h"/>
        <file src="fprime.c"/>
        <file src="fprime.h"/>
        <license><![CDATA[
These files have been placed into the Public Domain.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="Fietkau-BSD-ISS-IBM">
        <file src="base64.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2015 Felix Fietkau <nbd@openwrt.org>
Copyright (c) 1996 by Internet Software Consortium.
Copyright (c) 1995 by International Business Machines, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Permission to use, copy, modify, and/or distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES
WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR
ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.

---

Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND INTERNET SOFTWARE CONSORTIUM DISCLAIMS
ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTERNET SOFTWARE
CONSORTIUM BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR
PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS
ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS
SOFTWARE.

---
           
International Business Machines, Inc. (hereinafter called IBM) grants
permission under its copyrights to use, copy, modify, and distribute this
Software with or without fee, provided that the above copyright notice and
all paragraphs of this notice appear in all copies, and that the name of IBM
not be used in connection with the marketing of any product incorporating
the Software or modifications thereof, without specific, written prior
permission.

To the extent it has a right to do so, IBM grants an immunity from suit
under its patents, if any, for the use, sale or manufacture of products to
the extent that such products are used for performing Domain Name System
dynamic updates in TCP/IP networks by means of the Software.  No immunity is
granted for any product per se or for any other function of any product.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", AND IBM DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES,
INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  IN NO EVENT SHALL IBM BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL,
DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER ARISING
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN
IF IBM IS APPRISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
</copyright>
