<copyright>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
(C) 1992-2018 by Bruce Korb
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-3+ or BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="autoopts/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
(C) 1992-2018 by Bruce Korb
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="autoopts/stdnoreturn.in.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright 2012-2018 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="autoopts/gettext.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1995-1998, 2000-2002, 2004-2006, 2009-2018 Free Software
Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="autoopts/parse-duration.*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008-2016 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="autoopts/intprops.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2001-2018 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-2+ or LGPL-3+ with libopts exception or BSD-3-clause with libopts exception">
        <file src="snprintfv/compat.h"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/filament.c"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/mem.h"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/filament.h"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/filament.in"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/format.c"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/Makefile.am"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/printf.c"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/printf.h"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/printf.in"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/stream.c"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/stream.h"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/stream.in"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/custom.c"/>
        <file src="snprintfv/mem.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1998, 1999, 2000, 2002, 2003 Gary V. Vaughan
some files originally by Paolo Bonzini, 2002
* Snprintfv is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
* modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as
* published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the
* License, or (at your option) any later version.
*
* Snprintfv program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
* General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses>.
*
* As a special exception to the GNU General Public License, if you
* distribute this file as part of a program that also links with and
* uses the libopts library from AutoGen, you may include it under
* the same distribution terms used by the libopts library.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-3+ or BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="autoopts/tpl/man2mdoc.pl"/>
        <file src="autoopts/tpl/mdoc2man.pl"/>
        <file src="autoopts/tpl/mdoc2texi.pl"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Harlan Stenn
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-3+ or BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="autoopts/tpl/Mdoc.pm"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Oliver Kindernay (GSoC project for NTP.org)
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="GPL-3+"><![CDATA[
AutoGen is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under
the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free
Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option)
any later version.

AutoGen is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY
WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more
details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="LGPL-2.1+"><![CDATA[
  This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
  it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by
  the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1, or (at your option)
  any later version.

  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="LGPL-3+"><![CDATA[
If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-3.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-clause"><![CDATA[
Here is the Modified Berkeley Software Distribution License:

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

  1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
     this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
  2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
     documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
  3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote products
     derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN
NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="GPL-2+"><![CDATA[
If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="LGPL-3+ with libopts exception"><![CDATA[
For LGPL-3+ see paragraph "License: LGPL-3+" above.

If you distribute this file as part of a program that also links with and
uses the libopts library from AutoGen, you may include it under
the same distribution terms used by the libopts library.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-clause with libopts exception"><![CDATA[
For BSD-3-clause see paragraph "License: BSD-3-clause" above.

If you distribute this file as part of a program that also links with and
uses the libopts library from AutoGen, you may include it under
the same distribution terms used by the libopts library.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
