<copyright>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-alike">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1985-1995 Ian F. Darwin
1994-2016 Christos Zoulas <christos@zoulas.com>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-alike">
        <file src="src/apprentice.c"/>
        <file src="src/ascmagic.c"/>
        <file src="src/asprintf.c"/>
        <file src="src/compress.c"/>
        <file src="src/dprintf.c"/>
        <file src="src/encoding.c"/>
        <file src="src/file.c"/>
        <file src="src/fsmagic.c"/>
        <file src="src/is_tar.c"/>
        <file src="src/print.c"/>
        <file src="src/softmagic.c"/>
        <file src="src/vasprintf.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Ian F. Darwin 1986-1995.
maintained 1995-present by Christos Zoulas and others.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-alike">
        <file src="src/funcs.c"/>
        <file src="src/magic.c"/>
        <file src="src/readelf.c"/>
        <file src="tests/test.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2003 Christos Zoulas
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="public-domain">
        <file src="src/apptype.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Eberhard Mattes
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-netbsd">
        <file src="src/cdf.c"/>
        <file src="src/cdf_time.c"/>
        <file src="src/der.c"/>
        <file src="src/der.h"/>
        <file src="src/readcdf.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008 Christos Zoulas
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-netbsd">
        <file src="src/getline.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2011 The NetBSD Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-netbsd">
        <file src="src/fmtcheck.c"/>
        <file src="src/getopt_long.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2000 The NetBSD Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-Clause-regents">
        <file src="src/strcasestr.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1990, 1993 The Regents of the University of California
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="MIT-Old-Style-with-legal-disclaimer-2">
        <file src="src/strlcat.c"/>
        <file src="src/strlcpy.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1998 Todd C. Miller <Todd.Miller@courtesan.com>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="BSD-2-Clause-alike"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice immediately at the beginning of the file, without modification,
   this list of conditions, and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS'' AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR
ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="public-domain"><![CDATA[
Written by Eberhard Mattes and put into the public domain
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-2-Clause-netbsd"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE NETBSD FOUNDATION, INC. AND CONTRIBUTORS
``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE FOUNDATION OR CONTRIBUTORS
BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF
SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-2-Clause-regents"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
3. Neither the name of the University nor the names of its contributors
   may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
   without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS'' AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="MIT-Old-Style-with-legal-disclaimer-2"><![CDATA[
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES
WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR
ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
