<copyright>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2001-2004, 2010, 2012-2018, g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="src/b64dec.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008, 2011 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
2008, 2011, 2016 g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+ or BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="src/estream-printf.h"/>
        <file src="src/estream-printf.c"/>
        <file src="src/estream.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2004-2012, 2014-2017 g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="src/w32-estream.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2000 Werner Koch (dd9jn)
2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2007, 2010, 2016 g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="src/gettext.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1995-1998, 2000-2002 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="g10-permissive">
        <file src="src/gpg-error-config.in"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1999, 2002, 2003 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="g10-permissive">
        <file src="src/mkheader.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2010 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
2014 g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="src/posix-lock.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2005-2009 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
2014 g10 Code GmbH
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1+">
        <file src="src/w32-gettext.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1995, 1996, 1997, 1999, 2005, 2007, 2008, 2010 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="doc/yat2m.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2005, 2013, 2015, 2016 g10 Code GmbH
2006, 2008, 2011 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="g10-permissive">
        <file src="potomo"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008 g10 Code GmbH
2010 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="g10-permissive"><![CDATA[
This file is free software; as a special exception the author gives
unlimited permission to copy and/or distribute it, with or without
modifications, as long as this notice is preserved.

This file is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, to the extent permitted by law; without even the
implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="LGPL-2.1+"><![CDATA[
This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as
published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public
License along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="GPL-3+"><![CDATA[
This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, see <https://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-clause"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, and the entire permission notice in its entirety,
   including the disclaimer of warranties.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote
   products derived from this software without specific prior
   written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
