<copyright>
    <files license="FLEX">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2001-2008 The Flex Project.
Copyright (C) 1990, 1993, 1997 The Regents of the University of California.
All rights reserved.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="FSF-permissive">
        <file src="m4/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1994-2015, Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="bonzini-custom">
        <file src="m4/ax_prog_cc_for_build.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2008, Paolo Bonzini <bonzini@gnu.org>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Copying and distribution of this file, with or without modification, are
permitted in any medium without royalty provided the copyright notice
and this notice are preserved. This file is offered as-is, without any
warranty.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="FSF-permissive">
        <file src="m4/libtool.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1996-2001, 2003-2015, Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="FSF-permissive">
        <file src="m4/ltoptions.m4"/>
        <file src="m4/ltsugar.m4"/>
        <file src="m4/lt~obsolete.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2004, 2005, 2007-2009, 2011-2015, Free Software
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="FSF-permissive">
        <file src="m4/nls.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1995-2003, 2005, 2006, 2008-2010, Free Software Foundation
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="drepper-custom">
        <file src="po/Makefile.in.in"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1995-1997, 2000-2007, 2009, 2010
  Ulrich Drepper <drepper@gnu.ai.mit.edu>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
This file can be copied and used freely without restrictions.  It can
be used in projects which are not available under the GNU General Public
License but which still want to provide support for the GNU gettext
functionality.

Please note that the actual code of GNU gettext is covered by the GNU
General Public License and is *not* in the public domain.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="FLEX">
        <file src="src/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1990, 1993, The Regents of the University of California.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-2-clause, None">
        <file src="src/Makefile.am"/>
        <file src="src/filter.c"/>
        <file src="src/flexint.h"/>
        <file src="src/libfl.pc.in"/>
        <file src="src/libmain.c"/>
        <file src="src/libyywrap.c"/>
        <file src="src/mkskel.sh"/>
        <file src="src/regex.c"/>
        <file src="src/scan.c"/>
        <file src="src/skel.c"/>
        <file src="src/version.h"/>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2+">
        <file src="src/gettext.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1995-1998, 2000-2002 Free Software Foundation, Inc
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
under the terms of the GNU Library General Public License as published
by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2, or (at your option)
any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
Library General Public License for more details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="src/parse.c"/>
        <file src="src/parse.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1984, 1989, 1990, 2000-2015, Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-2+">
        <file src="tools/git2cl"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2007, Luis Mondesi <lemsx1@gmail.com>
Copyright (C) 2007, 2008, Simon Josefsson <simon@josefsson.org>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
git2cl is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2, or (at your option)
any later version.

git2cl is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
General Public License for more details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <license handle="FSF-permissive"><![CDATA[
This file is free software; the Free Software Foundation
gives unlimited permission to copy and/or distribute it,
with or without modifications, as long as this notice is preserved.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="GPL-3+"><![CDATA[
This package is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This package is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-2-clause"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

Neither the name of the University nor the names of its contributors
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="FLEX"><![CDATA[
Flex carries the copyright used for BSD software, slightly modified
because it originated at the Lawrence Berkeley (not Livermore!) Laboratory,
which operates under a contract with the Department of Energy:

This code is derived from software contributed to Berkeley by
Vern Paxson.

The United States Government has rights in this work pursuant
to contract no. DE-AC03-76SF00098 between the United States
Department of Energy and the University of California.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

Neither the name of the University nor the names of its contributors
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE.

This basically says "do whatever you please with this software except
remove this notice or take advantage of the University's (or the flex
authors') name".

Note that the "flex.skl" scanner skeleton carries no copyright notice.
You are free to do whatever you please with scanners generated using flex;
for them, you are not even bound by the above copyright.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
