<copyright>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1984-2008 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+ and BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="lib/fts.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (c) 1990, 1993, 1994
     The Regents of the University of California.  All rights reserved.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+ and BSD-3-clause">
        <file src="lib/fts_.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (c) 1989, 1993
     The Regents of the University of California.  All rights reserved.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="lib/rand-isaac.[ch]"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1999-2006 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999 Colin Plumb.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+ and ISC">
        <file src="lib/inet_ntop.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2005, 2006  Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (c) 1996-1999 by Internet Software Consortium.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="FSF-permissive">
        <file src="m4/autobuild.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 2004, 2006, 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
This file is free software; the Free Software Foundation
gives unlimited permission to copy and/or distribute it,
with or without modifications, as long as this notice is preserved.

From Simon Josefsson
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="src/cut.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1997-2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (C) 1984 David M. Ihnat
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="src/dircolors.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1996-2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (C) 1994, 1995, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000 H. Peter Anvin
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="src/paste.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1997-2005 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (C) 1984 David M. Ihnat
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-3+">
        <file src="src/shred.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright (C) 1999-2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999 Colin Plumb.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GFDL-1.2+">
        <file src="doc/coreutils.texi"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
Copyright @copyright{} 1994-1996, 2000-2008 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document
under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.2 or
any later version published by the Free Software Foundation; with no
Invariant Sections, with no Front-Cover Texts, and with no Back-Cover
Texts.  A copy of the license is included in the section entitled ``GNU
Free Documentation License''.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <license handle="GPL-3"><![CDATA[
This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="ISC"><![CDATA[
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any
purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above
copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND INTERNET SOFTWARE CONSORTIUM DISCLAIMS
ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTERNET SOFTWARE
CONSORTIUM BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR
PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS
ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS
SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-clause"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
4. Neither the name of the University nor the names of its contributors
   may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
   without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS'' AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
