<copyright>
    <files license="GPL-2">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1991-2012 Linus Torvalds and many others
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPL-2+ or X11">
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370-d*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370-mirabox.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370-netgear*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370-rd.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-370-synology-ds213j.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-375*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-38*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-39*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/armada-xp*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/artpec6.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/at91sam9260ek.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/at91sam9xe.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/axp*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/berlin2*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/cros-ec-sbs.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/cx92755*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/imx7*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/kirkwood-linkstation*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/ls*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/meson*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/mps2*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/mvebu-linkstation-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/orion5x-kuroboxpro.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/orion5x-linkstation*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/orion5x-ls*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/qcom-mdm9615*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/rk*.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/sama5d2.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/sama5d4.dtsi"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/socfpga_cyclone5_vining_fpga.dts"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/stm*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/sun*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/tegra124-apalis*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/uniphier-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/vf610-colibri*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm/boot/dts/vf610m*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/allwinner/*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/amlogic/*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/cavium/thunder-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/freescale/fsl-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/marvell/armada-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/marvell/berlin4ct-*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/rockchip/rk33*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/socionext/uniphier-ld*.dts*"/>
        <file src="arch/arm64/boot/dts/zte/zx296718*.dts*"/>
        <file src="include/dt-bindings/clock/sun*.h"/>
        <file src="include/dt-bindings/dma/axi-dmac.h"/>
        <file src="include/dt-bindings/dma/sun4i-a10.h"/>
        <file src="include/dt-bindings/pinctrl/sun4i-a10.h"/>
        <file src="include/dt-bindings/reset/sun*.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2012-2018 Linus Torvalds and many others
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="CRYPTOGAMS">
        <file src="drivers/crypto/vmx/*.pl"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2006,2014 Andy Polyakov <appro@openssl.org>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

* Redistributions of source code must retain copyright notices, this
  list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
  notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
  documentation and/or other materials provided with the
  distribution.
* Neither the name of the CRYPTOGAMS nor the names of its copyright
  holder and contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
  derived from this software without specific prior written
  permission.

ALTERNATIVELY, provided that this notice is retained in full, this
product may be distributed under the terms of the GNU General Public
License (GPL), in which case the provisions of the GPL apply INSTEAD
OF those given above.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER AND CONTRIBUTORS
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="Unicode-data">
        <file src="fs/nls/mac-*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
1991-2012 Unicode, Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
All rights reserved.  Distributed under the Terms of Use in
http://www.unicode.org/copyright.html.

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a
copy of the Unicode data files and any associated documentation (the "Data
Files") or Unicode software and any associated documentation (the
"Software") to deal in the Data Files or Software without restriction,
including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge,
publish, distribute, and/or sell copies of the Data Files or Software, and
to permit persons to whom the Data Files or Software are furnished to do
so, provided that (a) the above copyright notice(s) and this permission
notice appear with all copies of the Data Files or Software, (b) both the
above copyright notice(s) and this permission notice appear in associated
documentation, and (c) there is clear notice in each modified Data File or
in the Software as well as in the documentation associated with the Data
File(s) or Software that the data or software has been modified.

THE DATA FILES AND SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY
KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT OF
THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR HOLDERS
INCLUDED IN THIS NOTICE BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, OR ANY SPECIAL INDIRECT
OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF
USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR
OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR
PERFORMANCE OF THE DATA FILES OR SOFTWARE.

Except as contained in this notice, the name of a copyright holder shall
not be used in advertising or otherwise to promote the sale, use or other
dealings in these Data Files or Software without prior written
authorization of the copyright holder.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="Xen-interface">
        <file src="include/xen/interface/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2002-2006 Keir Fraser
2004 Tim Deegan
2004 Andrew Warfield
2005 Nguyen Anh Quynh
2005-2006 IBM Corporation
2005 Anthony Liguori
2005 Rusty Russell
2005-2006 XenSource Ltd.
2006 Ian Campbell
2006 Red Hat, Inc.
2010 Ryan Wilson
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to
deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the
rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or
sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER
DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="LGPL-2.1">
        <file src="scripts/extract-cert.c"/>
        <file src="scripts/sign-file.c"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2014-2015 Red Hat, Inc.
2015 Intel Corporation
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="GPL-2"><![CDATA[
This package is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License version 2 as
published by the Free Software Foundation.

This package is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this package; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301 USA

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="LGPL-2.1"><![CDATA[
This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
Lesser General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License
along with this program; If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="GPL-2+ or X11"><![CDATA[
This file is dual-licensed: you can use it either under the terms
of the GPL or the X11 license, at your option. Note that this dual
licensing only applies to this file, and not this project as a
whole.

 a) This file is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
    modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as
    published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the
    License, or (at your option) any later version.

    This file is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.

Or, alternatively,

 b) Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person
    obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation
    files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without
    restriction, including without limitation the rights to use,
    copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or
    sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
    Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following
    conditions:

    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
    included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

    THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
    EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES
    OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
    NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT
    HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
    WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
    FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR
    OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
