<copyright>
    <files license="BSD-3-Clause~Google">
        <file src="*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008-2018 Google Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-3-Clause~Bloomberg">
        <file src="src/google/protobuf/stubs/atomicops_internals_power.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2014 Bloomberg Finance LP
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="BSD-3-Clause~RedHat">
        <file src="src/google/protobuf/stubs/atomicops_internals_generic_gcc.h"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2013 Red Hat Inc
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="GPLWithACException">
        <file src="m4/acx_pthread.m4"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2006 Steven G. Johnson <stevenj@alum.mit.edu>
        ]]></copyright-notice>
        <license><![CDATA[
This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free
Software Foundation. As a special exception, the respective Autoconf
Macro's copyright owner gives unlimited permission to copy, distribute and
modify the configure scripts that are the output of Autoconf when
processing the Macro. You need not follow the terms of the GNU General
Public License when using or distributing such scripts.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt

to view the full license text.
        ]]></license>
    </files>
    <files license="Apache-2.0">
        <file src="python/mox.py"/>
        <file src="python/stubout.py"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2008 Google Inc.
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <files license="Public-Domain or Expat">
        <file src="conformance/third_party/jsoncpp/*"/>
        <copyright-notice><![CDATA[
2007-2010 Baptiste Lepilleur
        ]]></copyright-notice>
    </files>
    <license handle="Public-Domain"><![CDATA[
The author explicitly disclaims copyright in all jurisdictions which
recognize such a disclaimer. In such jurisdictions, this software is
released into the Public Domain.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="Expat"><![CDATA[
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-Clause~Google"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:

   * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
   * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
     copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
     in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
     distribution.
   * Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its
     contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
     this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-Clause~Bloomberg"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:

    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
      copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
      in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
      distribution.
    * Neither the name of Bloomberg Finance LP. nor the names of its
      contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
      this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="BSD-3-Clause~RedHat"><![CDATA[
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:

    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
      copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
      in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
      distribution.
    * Neither the name of Red Hat Inc. nor the names of its
      contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
      this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="Apache-2.0"><![CDATA[
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
    ]]></license>
    <license handle="GPL-3"><![CDATA[
This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, version 3 of the License.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

If you cannot locate the license in the source package, please visit

    https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt

to view the full license text.
    ]]></license>
</copyright>
